Look at this Look, in
Вы посмотрите вот вот на это Гляньте
short, this is an elite army standard
короче это элитный армейский норматив
[music] let's
[музыка]
go the master will show you how it should be
погнали мастер покажет как надо
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
[music]
[музыка]
close the sandals What are you doing Here we need to shoot Let's go I'm
закрывать санды ты что делаешь Тут нам
putting aside a valuable
снимать надо пойдём откладываю ценный
product in Africa there is no water I want to
продукт в Африке воды нет вот хочу
send Listen, man, this is all good of course
отправлять Слушай мужик это конечно всё
but it will melt in the spring there will be nothing
хорошо но он по весне растает вообще
left at all nothing If you put it aside it will melt melt melt
ничего не останется ничего не Отложишь
And the further
он будет таять таять таять И чем дальше
the more And what to do, in short, man, this
тем больше И что делать короче мужик вот
snow, all these, all these
этот вот снег вот эти вот все вот эти
reserves, banks at home, in short,
вот запасы банки дома короче там в
storing them in a mattress is already the last century
матрасе хранить это уже прошлый век
now everyone has been investing in cryptocurrency for a long time
сейчас уже давно все в криптовалюту
What is this I have
вкладываются Что это такое Я ничего-то
n't heard anything about rubles, I know all this is yuan
не слышал рубли знаю вот это всё юань
kuan And where can I get information Look, look at the
куань А где взять информацию Вот смотри
currency.com application Look, this is a
приложение currency.com Смотри это
fully regulated trading
полностью регулируемая торговая
platform that allows you to make
платформа которая позволяет Совершать
stock transactions and also invest in
сделки стоки а также инвестировать в
popular tokenized exchange
популярные токенизированные биржевые
assets and cryptocurrency There you can
активы и криптовалюту там ты можешь
trade all known
торговать всеми известными
cryptocurrencies such as bitcoins and
криптовалютами такими как биткоины и
ether and also invest Well, or how
эфир а также инвестировать Ну или как
option you can buy yourself
вариант ты можешь купить себе
tokenized Amazon shares damn
токенизированные акции Amazon блин это
this is all very cool and how to understand
это всё очень круто а как разобраться
this snow is simple But this is
вообще в этом снег-то простой А вот это
very difficult on kankom there is a
очень сложно на канком существует
separate training section with YouTube and
отдельный обучающий раздел с YouTube и
Telegram channels as well as with
Telegram каналами а также с анализами
stock market analysis moreover at first
биржевого рынка более того первое время
trading you can learn on a demo
торговли ты можешь обучаться на демо
account which is not at all from the real one
аккаунте который ничем не от настоящего
now on car.com there is an advertising
сейчас на car.com проходит рекламная
campaign invite a friend and both will receive a
акция пригласи друга и оба получите
bonus for this to receive a bonus in the
бонус для этого чтобы получить бонус в
form of cryptocurrency to your account you need
виде криптовалюты на свой аккаунт нужно
first follow the link specified in the
первое перейти по ссылке указанной в
description in the comments under this video
описании в комментариях под этим видео
second go through registration and verification of
второе пройти регистрацию и верификацию
accounts send your own
аккаунты переслать собственную
referral link to your friends and
реферальную ссылку своим друзьям и
wait until they register
подождать пока они зарегистрируют
verifiability
верифицируемость
that we work Hello my dears my attention
что работаем Приветствую родные мо внима
with three of my legs first of all Come on You
с тремя своими ногами прежде всего Давай
know what let's start You look we
Знаешь че начнём Ты посмотри мы
are at an event organized by
находимся на мероприятия организованного
Kirill Igorevich Sarichev and Andrey
Кириллом игоревичем сарычевым и Андреем
Zaikin in short powerlifting with a bunch of
зайкины короче пауэрлифтинг с кучей
all sorts of activities Istra and in the kitchen and
всяческих активностей Истра и кухне и
arm wrestling and in the booth they beat faces and in the
армреслинг и в будке морды били и в
car they fought in short what not  was Taking
тачке боролись короче что только не было
advantage of the opportunity so to speak and
Пользуясь случаем так сказать и
powers we are here nakai lo ca
полномочиями мы сес находимся накай
n't even imagine this is
ло даже представить себе не можете это
Los Los from Belarus About the one
Лось Лось с Белоруссии Про того про
you wrote to me about so that I would
которого Вы мне писали чтоб я его
check him for fornication Unfortunately,
проверил на блуд К большому сожалению
this person's timing is limited,
тайминг у этого человека ограничен
so it will most likely
поэтому на блуд его скорее всего
not be possible to check him for fornication, but today we will
проверить не получится но мы сегодня
make a complex under his sensitive
сделаем комплекс под его чутким
guidance, that is, after all, we
руководством то есть всё-таки какую-то
need to snatch some part of the content Yes, that's
часть контента урвать то надо Да вот
why today we will urv him and make
поэтому сегодня мы его урв и сделаем
some kind of military-oriented
какой-нибудь военно направленный
complex Yes, some kind of well, as he likes,
комплекс Да какой-нибудь ну как он любит
yes, we will do all this, we will create That is, he,
да всё это сделаем сотворим То есть он
as a knowledgeable person, a master of sports in
как это знающий человек мастер спорта в
this matter, a master when working with his
этом деле мастер при работе со своим
weight Evgeny, what are you
весом Евгений ты что ты
doing I was passing by Look at this
делаешь Я так проходил мимо Посмотрите
Look at this in short, the same are the
Вот на это Гляньте короче такой же
same No, well, with you they are deeper they are
одинаковы Нет ну у тебя они глубже они
deeper See Look at me, you have straight
глубже Видишь Смотри у меня у тебя прям
bam, I have rubics in short, vi Feel
бамм у меня рубики короче ви Чувствуй
fat I don't often feel energy I have a
себя толстым не часто чувствую энергии
lot in reserve, actually Tell me
мно про запас собственно есть Расскажи
what kind of complex This is the one
что за комплекс Вот это
that seems to quickly
который кажется быстренько сейчас
plant now we start with bird push-ups  on the
засадит начинаем с пти отжиманий на
bars then 50 pull-ups then 50
брусьях затем 50 подтягиваний потом 50
jumping hands behind the head and you need to
выпрыгивания руки за голову и нужно
lift your feet off the ground as little as possible and
минимально оторвать ноги от земли и
finish with 50 push-ups from the floor in short a
заканчиваем 50 отжиманий от пола короче
good result is considered to be
хорошим результатом считается выйти из
excellent in six That is I will aim
шести отличным То есть я буду метить
there I I No well I'm not a Moose In short my
туда я я Не ну я не Лось Короче у меня
ass is so much heavier and I don't have such
такая [__] такая потяжелее и нету такого
skill in working with my own weight I like to
мастерства работы со своим весом Я люблю
work with my own weight but the level is still such that
со своим весом работать но уровень всё
we are [ __ ] to put it mildly
всё-таки у нас такой ебётся мягко говоря
there you have to be really strict or a little
там надо прям строго строго или немножко
dirt is ok because I
грязи можно потому что я сам по себе
do the exercise myself slightly With a little dirt there is
делаю упражнение слегка С лёгкой грязин
nothing wrong with that these are not
в этом ничего страшного нет это не
green berets this is an elite army
зелёные береты это элитный армейский
standard I will do the bars normally but
норматив я брус сделаю нормально но
after them I will light up the pull-ups and then we
подтягивание после них я прикурю а потом
will try push-ups on the rings so as
ещё отжимание попробуем на кольцах чтобы
not to interfere with Vitya Vitya will be here on the pedestal
не мешать Вите Витя будет здесь на тумбе
I am on the rings the rings are more difficult well let's
Я на кольцах кольца посложнее ну
try nothing to worry about it it is more difficult it is
попробуем ничего страшного сложнее это
like about 40 percent Probably I
как бы ну процентов на 40 Наверно я
think great
думаю здоро
we haven't started yet we are just lying In short
мы ещ не начали мы только пиздим Короче
which topic is 6 minutes  to go out This is a great
тема какая из 6 минут выйти Это отличный
result this is just an elite soldier I
результат это прямо вот элитный армеец Я
don't know soldier 9 minutes is good and 13 is
не знаю солдат 9 минут - это хорошо и 13
disabled What do you think in places who
- это инвалид Как думаешь по местам кто
will take what today hard hammer it out very
какое займёт сегодня жёстко заруби очень
interesting but here
интересно но здесь небольшое
Victor has a slight advantage Well as for me
преимущество у Виктора Ну как по мне
because if I have business on the rings
потому что сам если дел на кольцах
this is my
это у меня
strategy how it will turn out I don't know by 15
стратегия как получится я не знаю по 15
by 10 I probably 15 10 10 there something like that
по 10 я наверное 15 10 10 там как-то так
I think I'll break it and that's not a fact
я думаю разобью и то не факт
jumping into the passage push-ups I don't
выпрыгивание в проход отжимание Я не
know if I can do it well in the
знаю смогу ли я сделать качественно в
passage I think no probably in two I'll
проход Я думаю нет наверное в два я буду
do sour milk dirty dirty you'll do it we'll
делать кисло молочно грязно грязно будеш
see I don't know how I'm
делать посмотрим Я же не знаю как со
doing from the outside Maybe I'm
стороны делаю Может я
[ __ ] awesome I don't know in terms of condition there is no strategy at all
охуительные не знаю по состоянию вообще
look my
стратегии нет смотри у меня уже вон
pulse is already 97 and 103 105 I can just about the
пульс 97 а 103 105 я могуть просто о
complex it will rise I saw And
комплексе он будет подниматься видел А
what is this Well look here just
что за это А ну это смотри тут просто
now we will do bars they will
сейчас мы будем делать бруси они будут
wash the brush Well because this is not
вымывать кисть Ну из-за того что это не
quite bars and this  like it holds you
совсем бруси и это как бы придерживает
a little so you don't get distracted special
немножко чтобы не отвлекало специальные
wristbands from the BL Shop store just like that
напульсники с магазина BL Shop прямо вот
twisted it loosened the tension they don't
так вот закрутил напряг ослабил они не
interfere wipe off your forehead if you're wearing a bandage
мешают со лба вытереть если повязку заб
sweat didn't
поте мне такие не
bother me Come on link in the description there's also a
помешали Давай ссылка в описании там ещё
promo code maybe you'll find yourself a discount
промокод может найдёшь себе на скидку
[music]
[музыка]
oh [ __ ] 2 1
охуе 2 1
let's go [music
погнали
]
[музыка]
I'm already tired [ __ ] dude right now
Я уже забился Бля чувак так сейчас
[music]
[аплодисменты]
tactics
тактика
11 that's what I was talking about [ __ ] butterfly
11 я про это и говорил бля баттерфляем
50 [ __ ] off At a time
50 нахуй За раз
[music] I'll
[музыка]
close
закрою
21 what are
21 чем
you rich in already 50 the
богат ти уже 50
hall can you do with such equipment at all
зал с такой техникой можно делать вообще
no With what Well with such everything is fine No everything is
нет С какой Ну с такой себе всё Нет всё
great Everything
отлично Всё
[music]
[музыка]
great
отлично
Handsome very powerful definitely in the green
Красава очень мощно точно в зелёные
berets you see the beret is already pulling for itself
береты возн видите берет уже себе тянет
green
зелёный
took 72 didn't get into the elite we condemn you
забрал 72 в элиту не попал осуждаем тебя
Senya  Zhenya said Normal As a feeling it is
Сеня Женя сказал Нормально Как ощущение
not hard at all Well like because I
вообще не тяжело Ну типа из-за того что
did pull-ups very slowly at the
подтягивание очень медленно делал в
end a little breathing but otherwise it is bearable
конце немножко дыхалка а так терпимо
just stretching can't be done faster
просто потягивание быстрее не сделать
ligaments everything here is buzzing after Arma
связки всё вот здесь загудели после Арма
Now I can't lift try write
Я теперь поднять не могу пробуйте пишите
your time cool complex write
своё время прикольный комплекс пишите
strictly not strictly pulled up from this the
строго не строго подтягивались от этого
main time depends on breathing for a
основное время зависит на подышать на
quick workout for those who are in a hurry
быструю тренировку для тех кто торопится
here 10 minutes basically another one like this in the evening and that's it and
вот 10 минут в принципе вечером ещ одну
you are a handsome man Like
такую же и всё и вы красавчик Как
yours I am home Belarus And the kids let's see
ваш я домой Беларусь А дети посмотрим
how your pulse is how much you bet
как у тебя пульс сколько ставки ставишь
he ended up doing it in
он в итоге его делал за
450 I think also somewhere in 5 minutes Yes
450 Я думаю также где-то из 5 минут Да
he could even do it faster
он может бы быстрее даже сделать изза
because now people are driven Adrenaline
того что сейчас народ драйв Адреналин
as if it would provoke more such another
как бы это более спровоцирует такая ещё
Atmosphere minutes from p need to make the
Атмосфера минут из п надо сделать
standard excellent need to do in 5
норматив на отлично надо сделать из 5
minutes I don't know how it will go here it is very
минут не знаю как пойдёт здесь очень
stuffy hot air there is nothing to worry about
душно жарко воздуха нет ничего страшного
the guys did it I have to do minutes Zhenya
пацаны сделали я должен сделать минуты
vat 3 2 Let's go Let's go let's
ження вать 3 2 Поехали Давай
go right away
погнал погнал сразу
let's go  let's
давай
go
погнал
op
оп
such
такой
Come on Davi
Давай Дави
Davi
Дави
[music]
[музыка]
332 I said I
332 Я же сказал не
can't I can't that means not at the maximum Well
могу не могу значит не на максимум дела
one there was just the atmosphere sog is
Ну один там просто был Атмосфера сог
restored very quickly back at
очень быстро восстанавливается обратно в
the moment was 182 it seems to be
моменте был 182 вроде бы быстро
restored quickly the heart is good the moose was
восстанавливается сердце хорошее у лося
standing still didn't want to think here is this
стоял ещ думать не хотел вот этот
guy here he is about it was
товарищ вот он
necessary
про надо было
also in training after the approach If
още во тренировки после подхода Если
you can reason to speak then in principle it's
можешь рассуждать говорить то в принципе
normal that's why I How from this thing and I train
норм поэтому я Как из этой штуки и треню
mainly by well-being tightened how much
осном по самочувствию затягивал сколько
you wait did 4010 I did it now
ты подожди сделал 4010 Сделал вот сейчас
I said just this master class in
я сказал как раз это мастер-класс на
fact if you give it a
самом деле если давать
kick it would be functionally harder to do that is
кипиння его функционально делать тяжелее
because I [ __ ] up well
было бы то есть из-за того что я проёб
like clogged I couldn't do it strictly
ну типа забитость не мог делать строго
That is it turns out I was resting And that's exactly why there
То есть получается я отдыхал И вот
was no such thing That
именно вот за дыки вот этой не было То
is if let's say m give King
есть если допустим м поддать Кинга
all the same then jumping like that
всё-таки потом выпрыгивание типа того
then push-ups that is the sensations would be
потом отжимание то есть ощущения были бы
more vomit maybe it would be less
более блевотным может было бы и меньше
But the sensations from the complex would be brighter
Но ощущения от комплекса были бы ярче
that's why I think it's worth it  redo
поэтому я думаю стоит его переделать
then try again as if well no No
потом ещё попробовать как бы ну не Нет
today we still have to wrestle there on our hands that is to say
сегодня нам ещё там на руках бороться то
hang in addition to these
есть ещё висеть помимо вот этих вот
complexes we will also do a small collaboration we will
комплексов ещё небольшую коллаборацию
drag Kirill there games and
сделаем затянем туда Кирилла игри и
hang him on a thick wide
повесим на толстом широком турнике
rotating horizontal bar Yes hard it will be
крутящемся Да жёстком это будет у
on Evgeniy's channel right Well I don't
Евгения на канале верно же Да вот я не
know Well a minute to hang seriously
знаю Ну минуту бы провисеть серьёзно
something [ __ ] nothing in front of the shoulders like let's do it
что-то нихуя пред плечи такие типа давай
without us You will go Well okay let's try
без нас Ты пойдёшь Ну ладно попробуем
what will happen the link to the horizontal bar on
что получится ссылка на турник на
Evgeniy will be in the description naturally
Евгения будет в описании естественно
also flies up to him on the channel he has a
тоже подлетает к нему на канал у него
lot of interesting things specifically
очень много интересного именно
sports purely sports so we will
спортивного чисто спортивного та мы
now rest and just go make
сейчас отдохнём и как раз пойдём делать
content to which we have now
контент на который мы сейчас здесь
left a link here all train [ __ ]
оставили ссылку всё тренируйтесь [__]
Don't be lazy you saw for yourself that in order to
Не ленитесь сами видели что для того
keep yourself in shape and
чтобы держать себя в форме и хорошо
look good You don't really need much time a
выглядит Не особо нужно и много времени
day for an hour hugged everything what else can you
в день по часу всё обнял что тут ещё
say Subscribe
скажешь Подписывайтесь
to the guys' channel on social networks if possible
на канал ребят на соцсети по возможности
to my channel with you were iron
на мой канал с вами были железные
masons Evgeniy  Elk wild elk Until next
масаны Евгений Лось дикий лось До новых
time, also fly to my channel to
встреч залетайте также на мой канал
watch a fight on a rotating horizontal bar there
посмотреть зарубу на крутящемся турнике
will probably be a cannon probably
будет пушечка наверное